[
    {
       "question":"The poem 'Baby Ate a Microchip' has been written by -",
       "choice1":"Neal Levin",
       "choice2": "William Wordsworth",
       "choice3": "Ruskin Bond",
       "choice4": "Robert Frost",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What did baby eat?",
       "choice1":"Microchip",
       "choice2":"Meal",
       "choice3":"Sugar",
       "choice4":"Bread",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"What did the baby catch all of a sudden?",
       "choice1":"A horse",
       "choice2": "A mosquito",
       "choice3": "A bug",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Neal Levin has written the poem - ",
       "choice1":"Daffodils",
       "choice2":"Baby Ate a Microchip",
       "choice3":"A Heritage of Trees",
       "choice4":"My Mother",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"In the peom 'Tower of Strength' the poet encourages us never to be - ",
       "choice1":"disappointed",
       "choice2": "aggresive",
       "choice3": "perplexed",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"In the peom 'Tower of Strength' the poet advises us turn our weakness into - ",
       "choice1":"boldness",
       "choice2":"strength",
       "choice3":"shyness",
       "choice4":"timidness",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":" 'Tornado' is a strong and ....... wind.",
       "choice1":"dangerous",
       "choice2": "soft",
       "choice3": "weak",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Thunder is a kind of .........",
       "choice1":"pain",
       "choice2":"tremble",
       "choice3":"help",
       "choice4":"disappointment",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"In the peom 'Tower of Strength' the poet encourages the person- ",
       "choice1":"to live the life of his dream",
       "choice2": "to live the life he has",
       "choice3": "to remain calm and quite",
       "choice4": "to remain contented",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":" 'Try, Try Again' has been written by-",
       "choice1":"Thomas Haig Palmer",
       "choice2":"R. L. B. Stevenson",
       "choice3":"David Horsburgh",
       "choice4":"Ruskin Bond",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"Thomas Haig Palmer is an ...... poet.",
       "choice1":"English",
       "choice2": "American",
       "choice3": "Australian",
       "choice4": "Scottish",
       "answer": 4
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Hard task will bring you ........",
       "choice1":"discontentment",
       "choice2":"hazard",
       "choice3":"sorrow",
       "choice4":"reward",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"Your courage will apear only when you try -",
       "choice1":"again and again",
       "choice2": "sometimes",
       "choice3": "never",
       "choice4": "without effort",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"One can do every thing with - ",
       "choice1":"patience",
       "choice2":"anger",
       "choice3":"calmness",
       "choice4":"frightened",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"How old was Suzuki when she stood in front of UN delegates?",
       "choice1":"thirteen years old ",
       "choice2": "twelve years old",
       "choice3": "fourteen years old",
       "choice4": "sixteen years old",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Why did the Taliban shoot Malala Yousafzai?",
       "choice1":"For promoting marriage for girls",
       "choice2":"For promoting jobs for girls",
       "choice3":"For promoting education for girls",
       "choice4":"For promoting sports for girls",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"UN Earth Summit in Rio-de-Janeiro was held in the year -",
       "choice1":"1991",
       "choice2": "1992",
       "choice3": "1893",
       "choice4": "1895",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"When Suzuki started an 'Environmental Children's Organization', she was just - ",
       "choice1":"Nine years old ",
       "choice2":"Eleven years old ",
       "choice3":"Ten years old",
       "choice4":"Eight years old",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"Who were asked to participate in the essay competition?",
       "choice1":"Preksha, Mohan and Shyama",
       "choice2": "Preksha, Sneha and Siddhartha",
       "choice3": "Siddhartha, Sneha and Shyama",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"The topic of Sneha's essay was - ",
       "choice1":"how to save money",
       "choice2":"how to save our earth",
       "choice3":"how to kill the enemy",
       "choice4":"how to protect our environment",
       "answer": 4
   }
   
   
   
   
   ]
